We might live 50 years longer, 100 years
longer, we don't have to die. I don't
think that we are there yet, and I also
don't think that there are any quick
fixes and wins. There is noise in the
system, and there is very, very good
science. So, what we have to do is
amplifying the real reality, doing the
trials, doing the education, building it
from the ground, and maybe diluting a
little bit the noise. Research entered
the phase of being in humans. We trialed
[music]
for decades if Metformin, if NMN, if
other gerotherapeutics [music] might
help in mice. And very often people say
we fixed mice. We have mice longevity
clinics, no problem.
And now we entered the arena that we can
also trial it in in humans. There are
many positive things [music] about the
field. The first thing is that we are
entering now a phase where we are not
only doing one intervention, [music] we
are now combining therapies to
antagonize aging process, and we call
that multi-modal intervention. Striving
[music] for better body functions,
better brain function, better heart
function. I think that's what we should
do.